
// Array of objects
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Which is considered as the most ancient part of the world by historians?',
        options: ['Gangetic Valley','Southern part of Vindhya Mountain','North Western Indian Valley', 'North Eastern part of India' ],
        answer: 'Southern part of Vindhya Mountain'
      },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'The State that comprises more number of Buddhist Viharas is',
        
        options:['Bihar','Karnataka','Jharkhand','Odisha'],
        answer: 'Bihar'
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:'The reign of Chandragupta Mauriya',
        options:['B.C. 324-299','B.C. 298-273','B.C. 261-236','B.C. 280-255'],
        answer: 'B.C. 324-299'
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:'The person who established British rule in India',
        options:['Robert Clive','Duplex',' Mirjafer','Hestings'],
        answer: 'Robert Clive'
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:'The official language of Pallavas was',
        options:['Tamil','Pali','Sanskrit','Kharosti'],
        answer: 'Sanskrit'
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:'The lines that adjoin different places with the same pressure are known as',
        options:['Contour','Isotherm','Isobar','Hythergraph'],
        answer: 'Isobar'
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:'In India, the National Human Rights Commission was established in the year',
        options:[' 1991','1993','1992','1994'],
        answer: '1993'
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:'Universally accepted colour for mountain is',
        options:['Gray','Snow White','Dark Green','Brown'],
        answer: 'Brown'
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:'Which Ocean has one third of land surface in the world:',
        options:['Indian Ocean','Arctic Ocean','Pacific Ocean','Atlantic Ocean'],
        answer: 'Pacific Ocean'
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:'The Article which deals with Education for All',
        options:['Article 41','Article 42',' Article 43','Article 45'],
        answer: 'Article 45'
    },
]